



As a **front-end developer** from a healthcare background, I am all about the user experience: I create clean designs with accessible and readable code, and value inclusive and welcoming environments. You can find me following tennis and Toronto's sports teams, as well as brushing up on languages inside and outside of tech.

t: 416-316-5108 | e: <u>sabine.tait@gmail.com</u>

Education

Immersive Web Development Bootcamp

Juno College 2021 - 2022

Honours Bachelor's of Science Human Kinetics

University of Guelph 2011 - 2015

Skills

Core

- Bilingual: English/French
- Clear & effective communicator
- Detail oriented
- Enthusiastic collaborator
- Thrives on organization

LIVE | REPO

Technical

- HTML5 / CSS3
- JavaScript (ES6)
- Sass
- RESTful APIs
- Responsive & accessible design
- React
- Firebase
- Version control, Git & Command line
- Paired/Peer programming

Projects

Art D'Oeuvre <u>LIVE | REPO</u> Willow <u>LIVE | REPO</u>

HTML5 | CSS3 | Sass | JavaScript | API Pair-project art gallery app that displays to the user a random art 'bite' fetched from the Walters Art Museum API

HTML5 | Sass | JavaScript Multi-page, responsive, blogger-style website PSD conversion project

Stars Align

React | CSS₃ | API

Horoscope app that allows the user to get their daily horoscope and other compatibilities with data from aztroAPI based on their astrological sign and the current date

Bite-Sized Traveling

LIVE | REPO

React | CSS3 | API | Firebase

Peer-programming travel app created based off a client brief allowing users to create trips and add/remove restaurants to their list based on their search locations. The user is also able to add notes to specific restaurants

Experience

Office Manager | First Care Centre

2015 - 2021

- Used refined communication and organization skills to manage 7 practitioners' schedules in order to maximize clinic hours and maintain a personable experience with patients
- Streamlined all patients' paper files to an updated digital web-based patient management system, and implemented electronic billing to over 85% Canadian insurance companies
- Updated social media pages and maintained accurate information on Google and OpenCare with office news, marketing material, and wellness tips to ensure community presence

Bilingual Seasonal Receptionist | Unique Gas Products

2012 - 2015

- Handled all consumer and dealer products inquiries (English/French), resolved complaints, facilitated returns, and directed fulfillment issues to the appropriate company personnel
- Supported sales/marketing teams in the organization and distribution of bilingual POP marketing material to North American dealers to successfully launch of 17 new products
- Key translator for technical support to facilitate communications with French speaking dealers and consumers